Hello everyone! I'm Anna Yamamoto from Equal Love and Maho Uesaka from Not Equal Me.
Today, Equal Love and Not Equal Me are currently collaborating,
We're here to visit Mage-san!
Ta-da!
Ta-da! Look at her.
Your mouth, your eyes,
And me, too, your face, Cubby!
Cubby!
Yes!
So, I've been told that I'm going to be filming a project.
I'm going to go.
I'm off!
Today's project is
Aim! Three in a row!
Meiji-san Sweets Derby!
Sweets derby! Sweets derby?
It's a sweets derby.
What is it?
This time, Equal Love and Not Equal Me are collaborating during Halloween.
This is a project with Mage.
We challenge our leaders to guess the top three sweets that each Iconoi member likes.
We, the leaders, are going to challenge ourselves.
It's a big responsibility, isn't it?
That's right.
So you have to guess what this member in the group likes, rather than what the group likes best?
Yes, that's right. For example, we get people asking us to guess Mirija's top three favourite snacks,
It might be a bit difficult,
But it's great!
Let's make her the enemy and do our best!
I'll do my best!
Yes, and the scoring, you have to predict which sweets will be in first to third place, and if the sweets you choose are in, you get one point, even if they are not in the same order.
Yes, and you score points.
And if you guess the exact order from first to third place, you've achieved a three-way tie.
I see.
You get 10 points.
So that's the trifecta.
That's right.
So if I guess that one of the sweets is number one, but it's in the top three, then I get points, right?
That's right, you get one point.
I see. By the way, it seems that Meiji will be giving a set of sweets to the person with the highest final score after several members have taken part in the challenge.
Thank you very much. I'm starving!
I want to eat sweets every day and live. I want it all to be sweets.
Let's do our best. Yes, I will. By the way, I think it's difficult to predict without any information at all, so it looks like the staff interviewed the members beforehand.
So I would like to make a prediction after watching the VTR.
Yes, I'll try to make a prediction after watching the VTR.
So let's get started, shall we?
The first member is this girl.
OK.
Okay, now for my favourite Okashi top file.
But I wonder if you've already decided who the second member will be, because I'm sure you'll have the decisiveness, Ana, and I think you'll win my first and third place.
Third place?
What's so hard about it?
Today? You haven't eaten anything.
It's difficult.
Yesterday.
Convenience store.
I'll give you a hint.
I'm in.
I have something to eat every morning.
Oh, my God, you're right.
Oh, no.
Don't make me sound like an honor student.
There's something I definitely eat every morning.
Meiji-san's products.
Meiji's products.
That's number one.
What's your favorite colour?
Favorite colour?
Just give me a hint.
Thank you.
Is it green?
Oh.
That's good.
You gave me a great clue.
My favourite colour is green, which is an absolute lie.
This one.
I've never heard of it.
Then let's change it to green candy.
I'll change it to green candy... because it's so easy.
Green narrows it down.
Oh, great.
But you have to guess first and third.
I want to go home now.
I want to go home now, before Hitomi gets mad at me.
What shall I do?
I'm scared!
I don't know what to do.
I know everything about eyes.
Oh, that's wonderful.
Wow, I'm excited, too.
Let's write it down.
I'm here to tell you that Mo Eco and I are not going to get on well together, Bach, and I'm shocked.
Today we're wearing matching t-shirts, but I don't know if you noticed, but today we're fighting a battle.
It's a battle.
I've only seen Hitomi-san eating sweets in Iconoi Juy,
Well, I think it's a bit difficult to watch three in a row, so I'm going to make a bet that I hope I'm in the top three.
I've made a bet.
Shall we send them all at once then?
Let's do it!
Ta-da!
I'm first in line for the Chocolate Effect 72% cocoa.
And second place goes to Garbo.
Yeah, delicious.
And third place goes to Chocobaby.
I've got three of Oh's!
For sure! The chocolate ones!
Yeah, something like, maybe, 72% cocoa.
I feel like I'm probably eating them first because they're good to eat in the morning or something.
And I think I liked it!
That's why I wrote this!
What about this, what about this?
Is that right? Is there such an answer?
I don't know. And?
Yes, I too have a 70% chocolate effect.
is good for you.
If I was going to have one, it would be this one.
And because it was green, I thought I'd try it.
So I decided to go for the green ones.
I'm not sure if I'm a mushroom person or a bamboo shoot person, but since it was just green, I decided to play green... Let's go! First of all, 4th and 5th place, by the way.
If it comes out here, you know...
Fourth and fifth.
No, don't answer!
Don't answer it, don't answer it, don't answer it.
Oh, my God.
Oh!
Fourth and fifth.
Cajoule and Whitefull.
Gummy stuff is good.
Gummies.
Pis.
I love them.
You didn't answer, because you're number two at the moment.
Oh, first place!
Next up is number one.
Okay, first place first.
Wait, I'm nervous.
Here's my favourite of all Meiji's sweets!
Ta-da! That's what I'm talking about! Chocolate toast! Yes!
I always have a piece of this every morning before I eat my meal.
This is what I was talking about! That's what I'm talking about! I love it!
Oh! Yes!
This is brilliant.
What?
Speaking of green...
It's Mr Bamboo Shoot Sugar.
I definitely like bamboo shoot sugar.
I always get gifts from Meiji-san at live concerts.
I sometimes receive gifts from Meiji-san.
We always get three boxes of bamboo shoot sugar.
Everyone always eats it. How's that? Oh! Ooh! Ooh! Ooh! Ooh! Ooh! Ooh! Ooh! Ooh! Ooh!
Ooh! Ooh! Ooh! Ooh! Ooh! Ooh! Ooh! Ooh! Ooh! Ooh! Okay, third place, I know this was hard, sorry. I'm a real wide-angle chocolate geek, so this is Maisie's.
It's the Venezuelan kind. Straight-up savoury chocolate.
It's really, really good. It's really, really good, folks.
There's four varieties of Maisie chocolates, and I really like the blue Venezuela box.
The cage is a bit pricey, but I recommend it.
123 is also three products. What is it? It's really... It's like you're not expecting it. Thank you very much.
I want to do this once.
I want to do it once.
Hai.
So I only got one right,
And the other one, what a surprise,
I got two ranks.
But I also guessed the first place,
But not here too?
That's for sure.
That's great.
The clues are really, really important.
Very important.
Okay, I'll do my best next time.
Okay, I'll do my best.
Then let's go to the next member.
This is the next one.
Here you go.
Tomi-chan.
Seven days.
What do you like, 7th?
Something you might not have guessed.
Why not!
Is that a clue video?
What do you think?
What about number one?
I don't think you'll ever guess number one.
You'll never win? I don't know.
Well, that's unexpected. Surprising, maybe, but if it were me, I'd probably say yes.
You know what?
Eh... After this.
Yeah. Wow.
Comment. Comment.
Yes, that's right.
You got the top three right.
I'm going to go and give you a pat on the shoulder,
It's alright.
Good luck with that.
A pat on the shoulder.
I'll just take it as a compliment.
Thank you.
This is not a hint. I don't need it as a hint at all.
It's not a clue at all.
No, really.
Let me guess.
Let's do it.
I'll play with you.
You play with me, I'll play back.
Mushrooms, bamboo shoots, ronso...
I don't have any, but I love them all,
We often talk about which one we prefer.
And Tomi and I are pretty much the same,
I see.
But he said he couldn't win,
I want to play.
I'll play too.
Yes, I'll play, I'll play, I'll play.
Okay, let's open it up, shall we?
Oh! I'm with you! I thought one of them would be in, so I wrote them both down, and the third one, I got Garbo chocolate in the first one earlier, but it wasn't in, so I tried again. Here.
It's delicious, isn't it?
I won because I just love it.
I also wanted to make a pile of mushrooms in first place.
I chose it because I'm a mushroom person and I wanted to make it, and also because I often get twinkle mushrooms at gigs and stuff.
I love twinkle mushrooms so much, and I used to eat them with Nanaka.
I'm sure that's it! I'll get a pat on the shoulder, won't I?
I want you to do that.
I'd like that.
What's next? Nissa chocolate third place goes to chocolate with a real flavour. It's the feeling that you really like it.
Let's have a quick look at the correct answer. Here you go.
First of all, fourth and fifth place.
Fifth place, right here.
Why?
And in fourth place, here's Se. Why?
It's Coffee Beat.
It's delicious.
Coffee Beet has been around since I was really little, since I was in kindergarten or so,
I used to buy one of the five in an assortment every so often,
I liked the coffee beets so much that I used to eat them on the way home from the bus, leaving the one with this flavour for last.
I would like to announce the first place!
First place goes to this!
Handmade.
Surprise!
I've never seen this before either.
What's that?
When I saw these lined up...
I was attracted to the packaging? Maybe...
It was the first thing I saw.
I thought if I knew about this, it would definitely be first.
I found out today.
It's number one.
Number one.
Oh, my God! Teachers are number one.
Indeed, and you guessed it.
I was just about to say number one.
What's the point of having an imaginative imagination?
What's this?
Imagination.
I knew it!
Look at this.
Mountains! Mountains! I'm from Pumpkin Maki, so look at that!
I'm from Pumpkin Maki.
Sakurajima!
An island?
What's going on?
This...
Sakurajima!
No, it's not! Oh, second place! Who's number two? Sakurajima! No!
Second place!
Second place.
Chocolate!
Wow!
That's a good guess, chocolate.
Put the cream on the bread.
Put some banana-flushed stuff on it.
I'll put a chocolate baby on it at the end.
I'm very happy.
I'm very happy to put a chocolate baby there.
I'm so happy to put a chocolate baby there.
I'm so happy.
And now I would like to go to the third place.
Third place goes to Mushroom Mountain.
I made Uchiras! Umimi-chan used to say "bachi" (bachi) in the Mushroom Mountain and Bamboo Shoot Village.
Recently, when I got a bit of a bumblebee with it...
She declared that it was definitely the mushroom mountain.
I thought that if I'd listened to her, I could have guessed another one.
I thought you might have guessed another one.
You're right, but I made it. I thought you might have guessed another one. You're right, though.
But I made it.
We made it. We made it.
We made it.
But once the handmade Apollo was on the list.
Wow, but it's frustrating.
It's frustrating, isn't it?
It's frustrating.
The other one was winning the Equal Love No., and mine was winning Mimi-chan's.
It's frustrating. This is. It's very frustrating.
Let's try again next time. Next time. Now let's get to the next member.
I'm a big fan of the first offensive type, and I'm more of a sweet person than a hard person, so I like them a lot.
I eat them almost every day.
Do you have a hard time deciding between them?
Yes, it's very difficult.
But when I say I like sweet things.
I think I've narrowed it down quite a bit. Hahahahahaha
Hahahaha.
When have you eaten strawberry sticks recently?
I ate them yesterday.
Yesterday? That's great.
Does Yamamoto-san look down there?
He's definitely looking.
He emphasises too much.
I'm sure he knows what you like best,
I'll be sad if I can't eat some of this. Definitely. Overemphasis. I was supposed to know your tastes best. Oh no.
Now, a bit,
It's amazing.
I'll be sad if I can't say it.
From a while ago, you've been amazing, Kirina.
I'm scared.
Kent, what's your favourite English word?
English word?
Sweet.
Sweet's cute.
That's great, but thank you so much for the hint.
That's very kind of you, the way you gave me the hint.
I can see a future where I'm going to get in trouble.
I'm sure Anchan saw you eat it.
Of course she's watching.
Hang in there, Neri.
Wait for me.
Wait, wait, wait.
Turn back the clock, it's me.
What was Risai eating then?
Risai?
In my memory.
Risai.
I met Risai.
Risai must have eaten this.
I gave it to her.
Here we go.
Ready.
Jankan.
I'll take Mushroom Mountain, Apollo and Swinkle.
I'm Apollo, Garbo chocolate pocket pack, Bamboo shoot village.
I'm already lost.
I understand.
Risa said on the lesson recently that she likes twinkle. I want that to be in there already.
Isn't that already a certainty?
I was torn between mushrooms and bamboo shoots for first place.
I was wondering which one it was too.
Let's see the correct answer.
The correct answer is here.
Fourth and fifth.
Fourth and fifth place?
Yes. Okay, first of all, fourth place.
Yes. This is fourth place first. Yes, this way. This way.
Yay!
There's a lot of different things in there, like compaitos,
I enjoy the thrill of it,
I'm still eating them all the time.
Fourth place! What a disappointment!
In fifth place,
This way!
Let's make it. Let's make it! It's the one from the "Let's make it!
I'm Apollo, the creator!
I made it a long time ago,
I thought it was great that I could make my own Apollo,
I love it and sometimes I make it.
My favourite pastry is...
Here it is.
I've already said really, really many times that I'm definitely a bamboo shoot, and
I wish I was eating them.
Oh, no, no, no!
In second place...
This one.
Apollo.
Oh, my God.
Apollo's been eating it since he was really little.
I try not to eat it all.
But then I realized it's always sweet like this.
He eats it all.
And when I make sweets.
I use it as an arrangement because it's cute.
2nd place.
It's sweet sweets.
Third place.
I'm really torn about third place, but you might think it's surprising.
Third place is coffee peat.
This might be difficult.
I love this coffee because it's savoury and it's really good with tea or something.
I really love chocolate, so it's all chocolate.
Indeed.
Colourful.
Oh no. I'm really sorry. Pear, I'm really sorry.
Risa, I'm sorry.
Aww.
Hey, I'm really sorry.
I was lost here all the way to the end.
Risa, I really love everything.
It's Risa...
That's why I'm so disappointed.
If it's Bamboo Shoot and Apollo...
I'd have won two in a row.
And this was fourth place, so it was so close.
I can't face Risa tomorrow. But I'm right about both Bamboo Shoot and Apollo.
I was paying attention, but it was in there! You really know your Ikoram!
Mouko has 4 points, Ko has 4 points, and I have 3 points.
Two more!
I'd like to make a trifecta soon.
We've only got 10 points.
Ten points.
If we have 10 points, we've already won.
I can eat a lot of chopsticks.
Let's see who's next.
Let's see who's next!
Let's start with Kanisawa.
Moe-chan has a snack that I really like,
That's why I'm so famous among the members of the amazing Mimi,
It might be a bit obvious.
I can tell. I know what Seira likes.
But they're there.
So they're there.
You're here?
Yes, they're here.
There might be.
Oh, no.
What did you watch on the video yesterday?
He's watching the VTR now,
I had yakiniku with Moe-chan, who's watching the VTR right now.
It was delicious.
It was a very enjoyable episode.
Not a clue at all. Wait, wait, wait.
It was fun. Give me a hint.
No, no, no. There was a video message.
Probably food in general. A lot of expensive food.
Yesterday, when Ono Moe and I went to the elementary and high school barbecue, I love beef tongue,
I ate a lot of beef tongue.
If you're looking for food, it might be a good hint.
Comment.
You have to guess!
I hate it!!!
I got it. I'm so happy!!!
Publicity!!! Publicity!
Thank you, publicity!
Oh, no? Sayaya.
It's enough that you just saw it.
I've already had it.
I'm so happy.
I'm sorry for interrupting your advertisement.
Sudden publicity.
I'm sorry. My tears.
Is that a hint? This is.
Tears.
This is a hint.
Let's write it down. But there's something about the sweets that Saya likes the most, that she likes the most,
I feel like there's something that's being passed on to Ecolleum.
I can tell.
I do.
I understand.
I don't know the order.
Indeed.
Speaking of sheaths, there's already something called sweet snacks.
Wow, I'm not sure.
Do you want to put it in playfully?
Have you written it?
Let's open it up.
Ready?
Wow.
That was close.
You scared me.
I thought I was going to go all the way.
Wow.
This could be a three-peat.
But is this right?
This and grape gummies would work, too.
I mean, she probably likes hard gummies, and she likes Coke.
And I think she eats a lot of Poyfuls.
It's right, isn't it?
I think it fits.
Really? - Yeah.
No, it's not.
It's just that the last one was either Apollo or Bamboo Shoot Surprise.
Right.
If Cair is a bamboo shooter...
Oh, you've already lost.
But, but, but,
If you can make all kinds of things,
Or if you can make a mountain of mushrooms like Saya and Usa,
I might probably choose this one.
Gentle.
I think there is.
Well, let's have a look.
Seen, go ahead.
Fourth and fifth place.
Will they come up?
First of all, fifth place!
Fifth place,
Garbo!
And in fourth place...
Poin!
These two,
Have one thing in common,
Once you open it, you can open it again.
It's packaged in such a way that you can do Pooh again.
I love it so much, I eat a lot of it all the time. They're packaged in such a way that you can open one and have another Pooh.
I love it so much, so much, so much - it's a Rafumiko wrap.
Let's make a snack of my favourite candy I was also interested in the mushroom mountain and I love it,
It's a sorah fumiko wrap, and I'm...
Feint?
Already us.
We're not anymore.
I love sorah gummies.
I love this kohlap.
I love it so much.
We eat it in Noemi's dressing room
I eat them.
Noe bought it for me.
I have a feeling she bought it.
An-chan recognized it, too.
Well done.
I knew it. Second place is a blank.
I'll give you second place.
Second place goes to...
Mr. Nakazawa.
We ate together, didn't we?
They were so good.
I ate it once and then ate it all at once.
I love them.
Anna, how are you now, Moe?
Are you getting it right?
Subtle.
One point.
Okay. - Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Third place.
I'd like to announce third place, yes, third place, I'd like to announce.
Third place goes to.
Takenaka no Sato.
No, it's not.
Now.
This is Moe-chan's.
I'm sure you know her.
Moe-chan's talking about mushroom skin.
You know what I'm talking about.
No, I told her that you didn't.
I know... that's the right response.
Wait, wait, wait, can I say one thing? What was this feint, this feint that wasn't first, second or third place?
It's really frustrating. I was just a bit confused, because when I went back to that bamboo grove, I got two of them right.
So it was only a Coke-up for both of you?
Yes, we did.
It was such a miracle we came in first place together.
What was all that excitement?
So the next member is the last.
Next up is the trifecta.
Let's go for it.
A trifecta for the both of us.
We'll do our best.
And now, our last member, this girl, is going to make it a trifecta! We'll do our best!
And now, our last member! This is the girl! Here she is!
Kiara!
I like sweet things and I also like bitter things.
Are you mature?
Well, I'm kind of broad.
But would you prefer the kind that doesn't leave an aftertaste to the kind that does?
Maybe not even that.
I don't know, I don't know.
It's hard to say.
What have you enjoyed recently?
I found a mountain I like.
That's a big clue.
Is this a clue?
I'm not good at it. Is the last one a big clue? Is this a clue? Maybe. Thank goodness.
Miracle.
A great big hint at the end.
I don't know how many places this will come in.
But it's the best because it has sweet, bitter and mountain in it.
KiharaSweet food suits you, but do you also like mature food?
KiharaSurprisingly, I often say that I've already had my say.
She says it more than you'd expect.
My tastes may also be mature.
Maybe I'm becoming an adult.
I've opened the door.
So that's the last one.
Let's have a look!
Seen!
It's quite different.
Oranjut Pouch.
Coffee beat.
Handmade arpoles.
Not at all disjointed?
Mushroom mountain
Garbonko.
Are you a chocolate baby mushroom man?
You said mountains.
I'm sure I forgot.
I didn't see a mountain of mushrooms anywhere.
That's such a good clue.
He said mushroom mountains.
I was going to ask you.
I thought it was sweet and bitter and I thought it was an adult selection and then I forgot.
I'm surprised at myself now. It's a great shock.
Now let's see what the correct answer is for the character.
Here it is.
First of all, it's fourth and fifth place.
You know that you don't want to appear here.
This way.
Galgal.
It's really delicious.
If I bought a big bag of these, I'd eat the whole thing, so I'm an adult party percent chocolate exchange Delicious I always eat 86% of them.
I always eat 86% of them, like when I want to concentrate.
I'm not sure if it's Hitomi, but she's No. 1, too.
I love it. I love it. I love it.
I love it.
Number one.
This is...
Oh!
It's my mum's favourite.
When I got a bite...
What kind of candy is this?
When I was a little girl.
I was shocked.
But they're a bit expensive.
That's why I couldn't eat much when I was little.
But I loved this one a bit more, and I tried my best backwards b Sure, I'd love it very much.
Mmm.
Mmm. - Mmm.
Okay, first place, red hair, red, second place...
The latest is No. 4.
Everyone used to be a bamboo shoots guy.
So you can see how delicious they both are. Absolutely now the time has come for takinokono-no-yama. A delicious mountain. By the way, I've taken off the mushrooms.
Oh, they are delicious, aren't they?
I love them.
I understand.
Maika loves them too.
Third place goes to.
Shuga gummies.
What shall I do with them?
What shall I do.
I think I'll go out and buy a camera.
What shall I do a bit really.
I don't know what to do. I like this one too, because a lot of kids like gummy bears.
I hope you all do too.
What's the last one?
Yes.
It's a sea-bun.
So I won one mushroom mountain, but in a different order.
I'm just so jeez, they were all different.
I'm sorry. Chiara-san.
I'm sorry. Kiara.
So, the results, the final results.
Mayuko, 5 points.
Anna, 5 points.
There's one. So, what a draw it was. Oh, oh, I'm sorry. Really. I am really sorry to all the members.
I have to learn very much as a leader.
I would like to take the time to see you all eating sweets in the future.
Let's keep looking at what everyone likes at the catering place from now on.
Let's check it out.
So we've had a look, how did you like it? Today, too.
Well, it's frustrating, but everything from Meiji-san is delicious,
I felt like it was all very, very good, so..,
I want to observe the members a bit more, and next time I want to take revenge.
Yes, really. I want to apologise to the members the next time we meet.
Oh, that's right.
I should apologise too.
Yes, that's right. But really,
I'm eating sweets like this, like this,
Like this, with sweets,
I was able to collaborate with a master,
I'm really happy to be able to shoot like this,
I feel really happy.
Thank you very much.
Please try the sweets that the members like.
So that's it, the Meiji-san sweets derby.
And once again, Equal Love and Not Equal Me are currently collaborating.
Please everyone also check out Meiji Milk Chocolate Cubby Halloween and Go Star Son Star Assorted Oat Halloween.
They are extremely tasty. Yes, they are.
And the packaging is really cute too. That's right. After all, these five as-autos have always been familiar to adults, haven't they?
They are familiar to adults, aren't they? They have eyes, holes and mouths, and it's fun to guess what they are.
This time, the theme of the collaboration is "sweets pretending",
We're going to use this kind of thing to bring a bit of playfulness to the collaboration,
Please take cute photos at Purikura and so on.
Please do.
There is also a pop-up here at the moment.
Have you seen it?
Have you seen it? Have you seen this?
This is the photo that you see all the time,
But between you and me,
You shot the visuals, didn't you?
That's right.
I'm sure it will be developed in the future, so please look forward to it.
Please look forward to it.
How's it going? How was the shoot?
We were surrounded by delicious snacks, and we also received gifts, so I think all the members have really happy faces.
That's right. I also wondered if some of the girls might or might not have a slightly rare hairstyle in Equal Love.
Actually, Noeri may or may not be one of them. ah Thank you very much.